wowinterface.com 2007-07-23

# OGaming - OGaming Network Privacy Policy

### 

Effective Date: October 11, 2005 

**The OGaming Network** , which is comprised of the websites listed [here](http://www.ogaming.com/data/3176~NetworkSites.php), and the OGaming Store, located at [here](http://www.ogamingstore.com/) (The OGaming Network and the OGaming Store collectively, "OGaming"), respect your privacy rights and recognize the importance of protecting the Personal Information (as defined below) provided by you to OGaming. This Privacy Policy describes how OGaming collects, stores, and uses the Personal Information you provide to OGaming through the OGaming Network Web sites, the OGaming Store, and through telephone or e-mail communications you may have with OGaming. This Privacy Policy also describes the choices available to you regarding OGaming's use of the Personal Information you provide to OGaming, and the actions you can take to access this information and request that OGaming correct or delete it. 

### Consent 

By using the OGaming Store Web site, or any of the OGaming Network Web sites, you acknowledge that you have read this Privacy Policy and you consent to the practices described herein with respect to OGaming's collection, use and disclosure the Personal Information provided by you to OGaming. This is OGaming's entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. The OGaming Store reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy in accordance with the terms herein at any time, which is why OGaming encourages you to visit this page often, review this Privacy Policy frequently, and remain informed about any changes to it. 

If, after review, you still have questions about any portion of this Privacy Policy, please contact OGaming using the contact information provided at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. 

### Information Collection and Use 

**Personal Information**

“Personal Information” means information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, or other contact information, whether at work or at home. 

On all OGaming Web sites that collect Personal Information, we specifically describe what information is required in order to provide you with the product, service, or feature you have requested. 

OGaming collects Personal Information when you contact OGaming, when you register with the OGaming Network, when you use OGaming products and services, when you submit an order with the OGaming Store to purchase products offered for sale, when you visit the OGaming Web sites or the Web sites of certain OGaming partners, and when you enter promotions and sweepstakes. 

_Registration_

You are required to register with OGaming in order to use selected features of the OGaming Network, such as being able to posting messages on OGaming forums. In order to register, you must first complete the on-line registration form, which requires you to create a username and password. During registration, you are also required to provide Personal Information, such as your e-mail address and birth date, so that we may contact you about the services on the site(s) in which you have expressed interest and so that we may verify your age. 

During registration, you will also have the option to provide additional Personal Information, such as your homepage, your instant messenger handle(s) and additional e-mail addresses. OGaming will make this information viewable by other users of the OGaming Network to facilitate interaction between you and other users of the OGaming Network. 

_The OGaming Store_

The OGaming Store only collects Personal Information from you on a voluntary basis and only that information necessary to facilitate the completion of an order. Personal Information collected is not limited to, but may include: name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, and credit Card expiration date. 

_Promotions, Contests and Sweepstakes_

From time-to-time, OGaming may provide you the opportunity to participate in promotions, contests or sweepstakes on the OGaming Web site(s). Such promotions, contests and sweepstakes will also be governed by the rules and regulations posted with such promotions, contests and sweepstakes. If you participate, you will be required to register with OGaming, which will require you to provide certain Personal Information. Participation in these promotions, contests and sweepstakes is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to register and provide your Personal Information. The requested information typically includes contact information, such as name, shipping address, e-mail address, and telephone number. OGaming will use this information to notify winners and award prizes. Additionally, during your registration process you may opt-in to receiving additional related communications from OGaming. If you decide to opt-in, OGaming will use the information provided to send you communications described throughout this Privacy Policy. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications (please see the "Choice and Opt-Out" section of this Privacy Policy) if at any time you decide you do not wish to receive such communications. 

_Newsletters_

If you wish to subscribe to the OGaming newsletter(s), OGaming will use your name and e-mail address to send the newsletters to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications (please see the "Choice and Opt-Out" section of this Privacy Policy). 

**Other Information Collected**

Some information may be collected automatically every time you visit the OGaming Web sites, such as cookies and computer information. In addition, information may be collected from other independent, third-party sources. OGaming also collects information about which pages you visit within OGaming. This site visitation data is identified only by a unique URL. 

_Cookies_

OGaming uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies as part of its interaction with your browser. A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier (a file) that OGaming Web sites transfer to your computer’s hard drive through a Web browser to enable its systems to recognize your browser for record-keeping purposes. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser, while a persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. 

OGaming uses session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the OGaming Web sites. OGaming uses persistent cookies to identify and track which sections of its Web site you most often visit. OGaming also uses persistent cookies in areas of its Web site where you must register, and where you are able to customize the information you see, so that you don't have to enter your preferences more than once. OGaming cookies do not collect Personal Information and OGaming does not combine information collected through cookies with other Personal Information collected to determine your identity or a your e-mail address. 

By configuring the options in your browser, you may control how cookies are processed by your system. However, if you decline the use of cookies you may not be able to use certain features on OGaming Web sites and you may be required to reenter the information required to complete an order during new or interrupted browser sessions _._

Some of OGaming's business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on the OGaming Web sites. OGaming has no access to or control over these cookies (see "Third Party Advertising" and "Third Party Cookies" below). Accordingly, this Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by OGaming only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

OGAMING DOES NOT DISCLOSE ITS COOKIES TO THIRD PARTIES EXCEPT AS REQUIRED BY A VALID LEGAL PROCESS SUCH AS: SEARCH WARRANT, SUBPOENA, JURISDICTIONAL STATUTE, OR COURT ORDER. 

_Log Files_

As is true of most Web sites, OGaming gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet services provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. OGaming uses this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the OGaming Web sites, to track users' movements around the Web sites and to gather demographic information about OGaming's user base as a whole. OGaming does not combine information collected through log files with other Personal Information collected to determine your identity or your e-mail address. 

_Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)_

OGaming employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help OGaming better manage content on its Web sites by informing OGaming what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. OGaming does not combine information collected through clear gifs with other Personal Information collected to determine your identity or your e-mail address. 

OGaming uses clear gifs in its HTML-based e-mails to inform OGaming which e-mails have been opened by you. This allows OGaming to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of OGaming's marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these e-mails, please see "Choice and Opt-Out" section of this Privacy Policy. 

_Information from Third Party Sources_

To improve services and enhance personalization, OGaming may periodically obtain information about you from other independent third party sources and add it to our account information. For example, when you visit a site on which OGaming advertises, and click through such advertisement, OGaming may place cookies on your computer. 

_Third Party Advertising_

The ads appearing on the OGaming Web sites are delivered to you by DoubleClick, OGaming's Web advertising partner. Information about your visits to the sites, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address or other Personal Information), is used to serve ads to you. For more information about DoubleClick, the third party cookies, and how to "opt-out", [please click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/) [[http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/]](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/). 

_Third Party Cookies_

In the course of serving advertisements to the OGaming sites, OGaming third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your web browser. 

_Additional, DoubleClick, privacy information can be found at:_<http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/>  

_DoubleClick Opt Out_

This Web site uses the technology of DoubleClick Inc. to serve ads when you visit this site. DoubleClick may use non-personal information, such as your state or zip code, in order to provide advertisements while you visit this Web site about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, DoubleClick may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by DoubleClick,[ please click here ](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/). [[http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/]](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/)

**Use of Information**

_Verification, Billing, and Order Status_

OGaming collects Personal Information to verify the accuracy of your name, billing address, shipping address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date provided, and to bill you for products purchased. OGaming uses your e-mail address(es) to contact you regarding the status of your order when necessary and to send you a Receipt Purchase Confirmation and Order Shipping Notification. 

_Special Offers and Updates_

OGaming collects information about which sections of its Web site you visit most often, so that it can send you OGaming newsletter and information about relevant offers, promotions, contests, and sweepstakes which may interest you. 

Accordingly, OGaming will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions and sweepstakes. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications (please see the "Choice and Opt-Out" section of this Privacy Policy). 

_Service-related Announcements_

OGaming may, but is not obligated, to send you strictly service-related announcements or rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For example, if OGaming's service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, OGaming might send you an e-mail. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications since they are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you may have the option to deactivate your account. 

_Research_

OGaming also collects information for research purposes and to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. OGaming uses the information collected for its own internal marketing and demographic studies to improve customer service and product offerings. 

_Customer Service_

Based upon the Personal Information you provide to OGaming, OGaming will send you a welcoming e-mail to verify your username and password. OGaming will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. OGaming will communicate wit you by e-mail or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

_Preferences_

OGaming stores information that it collects through cookies, log files, and third party sources to create a profile of your preferences, in order to improve the content of the OGaming Web site for you. 

_Tax Purposes_

OGaming maintains and stores customer information for tax purposes as required by local, state, and federal statutes. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure 

OGaming does not sell or rent any of the information collected to third parties for any purposes, but it shares information with third parties as described below. 

_Service Providers_

OGaming discloses the information collected to external service providers necessary to facilitate the following outsourced operations: address verification, credit card processing, and order shipping. These external service providers are subject to confidentiality agreements with OGaming and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information OGaming provides them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced operations listed above. 

_Other Third Parties_

OGaming shares information, including Personal Information, with trusted third-party partners so that customers can receive information about third-party offers and promotions that may interest them. These third-party partners do not have independent rights to share the information provided to them by OGaming. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option under which you may opt-out of the sharing of your Personal Information for such purposes (please see the "Choice and Opt-Out" section of this Privacy Policy). 

_Compliance with Legal Authorities_

As required by law, and to enforce customers’, or OGaming's legal rights, and to comply with local, state, and federal law, OGaming may disclose information to law enforcement agencies. 

### Choice and Opt-Out 

OGaming provides you the opportunity to opt-in to having your Personal Information used for certain purposes, when OGaming asks for this information. For example, if you purchase a product from the OGaming Store you must indicate on the order form that you wish receive additional marketing materials from OGaming, such as e-mails regarding special offers, promotions, and sweepstakes ("opt-in"). 

If you no longer wish to receive OGaming's promotional communications, you may "opt-out" of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by e-mailing OGaming at [support@ogaming.com](mailto:support@ogaming.com). Additionally, if you have created an [Account](http://login.ogaming.com/register.php), you may “opt-out” of receiving promotional communications by selecting such option in the profile section of My Account. OGaming provides its customers with clear, simple and easy to follow remove instructions for unsubscribing from the OGaming mailing list. Mailings from an e-mail list cease when a remove email is received. Additionally, you may contact OGaming using the contact information provided at the bottom of this Privacy Policy to opt out. 

### Links to Other Web Sites 

There are several places throughout the OGaming Web sites that may link you to other Web sites that do not operate under this OGaming Privacy Policy. When you click through to these Web sites, this OGaming Privacy Policy no longer applies. OGaming recommends that you examine the privacy statements for all third party Web sites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your Personal Information. 

### Forums/Chat Rooms 

If you decide to post messages in the forums or chat rooms on the OGaming Web sites, you should be aware that any Personal Information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of such forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. OGaming is not responsible for the Personal Information you choose to submit in these forums and/or chat rooms. 

The use of the OGaming Web sites and all forums and chat rooms therein is governed by the OGaming Terms of Use, a copy of which is located [here](http://www.ogaming.com/data/2274~termsofuse.php), which is hereby incorporated by reference. In the event there exists any inconsistency between this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, regarding the use of information, the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement shall take precedence. 

OGaming reserves the right to terminate your membership with OGaming in the event you use the OGaming Web sites, including without limitation the forums and/or chat rooms, in a manner inconsistent with the OGaming Terms of Use. 

### Storage and Security of Personal Information 

**Storage**

OGaming stores the information it collects on computers located in a controlled, secure facility protected from physical or electronic unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. 

**Security**

OGaming protects the privacy and integrity of the information it collects by employing appropriate administrative protocols, technical safeguards, and physical security controls designed to limit access, detect and prevent the unauthorized access, improper disclosure, alteration, or destruction of the information under its control. OGaming transmits the information used by its external service providers for the specific outsourced operations listed above across public and private networks via recognized encryption technologies, such as by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you input. 

Although OGaming follows the procedures set forth above to protect the Personal Information submitted to OGaming, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Thus, while OGaming strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, OGaming cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about OGaming's security on the OGaming Web sites, please feel free to send us an e-mail at [support@ogaming.com](mailto:support@ogaming.com). 

_Internet Fraud_

OGaming has a ZERO TOLERANCE policy for Internet fraud or any attempt to access or acquire customer or other information on its Web sites via illegal or surreptitious means. OGaming works with local, national, and international fraud investigation agencies and employs a variety of electronic and other means to discourage, detect, and intercept fraudulent activities. OGaming aggressively prosecutes, to the fullest extent of the law, those perpetrators apprehended conducting fraudulent activities on its Web site. 

Agencies with which OGaming cooperates are: state and local police authorities, the Federal Bureau of Investigation, UPS, US and International Customs Agencies, and Interpol. 

_Email Abuse_

OGaming has a ZERO TOLERANCE policy for e-mail abuse. OGaming e-mail mailing list administrators take strong measures to ensure that such mailing lists are NOT used for abusive purposes. Further, OGaming e-mail mailing list administrators maintain an "Ignore List" of e-mail addresses from which all information inquiries are ignored. E-mail addresses are added to the Ignore List when OGaming e-mail mailing list administrators receive abusive or otherwise inappropriate email from listed e-mail addresses. 

### Access and Update of Information 

**OGaming Account**

OGaming provides account as a means for you to access and ensure that your information on file with OGaming is current and accurate. You may opt-in to creating an account when you are prompted for, and provide, certain Personal Information, such as your name, address, telephone number, and/or e-mail address, in conjunction with your use of areas of OGaming that require such Personal Information. If you decide to create an account, you may review and/or update information on file in your account by using your username and password to login to your account. 

If you have not created an account and wish to review and/or update the information on file with OGaming, you may e-mail OGaming at [support@ogaming.com](mailto:support@ogaming.com). 

### Legal Disclaimer 

The OGaming Web sites operate "AS IS" and "As Available," without liability to OGaming of any kind. OGaming is not responsible for events beyond its direct control. 

Back to Top 

### Ownership and Assignment 

OGaming is the sole owner of the information collected on the OGaming Web sites, including without limitation the Personal Information, and as such, OGaming may transfer or assign any and all of such information to a third party in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of all or substantially all of OGaming’s assets, provided that in such an event OGaming will provide you with a notice before information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Such notice will provide a description of the changes, and your options with respect to such a change in the privacy policy. OGaming may also transfer or assign such information in connection with a bankruptcy order. 

### International Transfer 

Personal Information collected by OGaming may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which OGaming or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the OGaming Web sites, you consent to any such transfer of Personal Information outside of your country. 

### Children 

The OGaming sites are not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 13. OGaming does not sell products for purchase by children. Any person who provides their information to OGaming through the OGaming Web sites represents to OGaming that they are 13 years of age or older. 

### Changes to this Statement 

OGaming will from time-to-time update this Privacy Policy, each time revising the last updated date at the top of the Privacy Policy and indicate the nature of the revisions within the statement. OGaming will notify customers of material changes to this statement by e-mail or by placing prominent notice on the OGaming Web site. 

### Questions & Comments 

If you have questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact OGaming using the contact information at the bottom of this Privacy Policy, and OGaming will use all reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem. 

### Contact Information 

You may contact OGaming by e-mail at [support@ogaming.com](mailto:support@ogaming.com). Additionally, you may write to OGaming at:

OGAMING NETWORK, LLC.  
8900 Wilshire Blvd., Suite 200   
Beverly Hills, CA. 90211
